{
  "id": 1,
  "class": "Lớp 5",
  "semester": "Cuối học kì 1 - Bài kiểm tra số 1",
  "dataList": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "What is the highest among the answer below?",
      "answer": "b",
      "a": "5 centimeters",
      "b": "20 meters",
      "c": "200 centimeters",
      "d": "100 decimeters"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What was the matter with him? He........ a toothache",
      "answer": "d",
      "a": "to have   ",
      "b": "have",
      "c": "has",
      "d": "had"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "What subject is he......... now? Vietnamese.",
      "answer": "c",
      "a": "to learn",
      "b": "learn",
      "c": "learning",
      "d": "learned"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "............ did she go yesterday morning? She went to the bookshop.",
      "answer": "b",
      "a": "What",
      "b": "Where",
      "c": "When",
      "d": "Why"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Are you free........ the evening? Yes, I am.",
      "answer": "b",
      "a": "in",
      "b": "on",
      "c": "at",
      "d": "to"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "She is going to......... television tonight.",
      "answer": "d",
      "a": "sing",
      "b": "play",
      "c": "stay",
      "d": "watch"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "............ is that ? It's my teacher.",
      "answer": "b",
      "a": "What",
      "b": "Who",
      "c": "Where",
      "d": "How"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Does she like sandwiches ?......................",
      "answer": "c",
      "a": "Yes, she do",
      "b": "Yes, she is",
      "c": "Yes, she does",
      "d": "Yes, she like"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "This is Mai.............. mother is a doctor.",
      "answer": "c",
      "a": "his",
      "b": "she",
      "c": "her",
      "d": "he"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "She............. a banana.",
      "answer": "a",
      "a": "wants",
      "b": "want",
      "c": "to want",
      "d": "wantes"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "He is................... Vietnam",
      "answer": "a",
      "a": "from",
      "b": "on",
      "c": "in",
      "d": "at"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "............ is that ? It's my teacher.",
      "answer": "b",
      "a": "What",
      "b": "Who",
      "c": "Where",
      "d": "How"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "................... you like to play hide and seek with me?",
      "answer": "d",
      "a": "are",
      "b": "where",
      "c": "does",
      "d": "do"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Did you....................... teacher's Day last month?",
      "answer": "c",
      "a": "celebrated",
      "b": "celebrating",
      "c": "celebrate",
      "d": "celebrater"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Does he........................ a sore-throat?",
      "answer": "c",
      "a": "has",
      "b": "had",
      "c": "have",
      "d": "having"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "We went to the cinema....................",
      "answer": "b",
      "a": "today",
      "b": "yesterday",
      "c": "tomorrow",
      "d": "next Sunday"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "A housewife often does......................",
      "answer": "c",
      "a": "homework",
      "b": "hardwork",
      "c": "housework",
      "d": "exercises"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "It's hot in Summer,..................... ?",
      "answer": "b",
      "a": "is it",
      "b": "isn't it",
      "c": "do it",
      "d": "does it"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "...... your birthday? It's in May.",
      "answer": "b",
      "a": "What's",
      "b": "When's",
      "c": "It's",
      "d": "Where's"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "Would you like..... milk? No, thanks",
      "answer": "c",
      "a": "an",
      "b": "a",
      "c": "some",
      "d": "one"
    }
  ]
}
